<?xml version="1.0"?>
<contentList xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <content contentuid="h852ed21cga23ag44b3gac83g3bff6a430bea" version="1">The Angel of the Seven Heavens is the dragon god of justice. His ideals of mercy and just authority keep him locked in an inexorable rivalry with his sister, Tiamat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Life, War&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Lawful Good</content>
    <content contentuid="hea607a6ag159dg4729gad41g5b0de1de365c" version="2">Creator of the elves, Corellon Larethian oversees the elven pantheon as a whole, providing blessings to those who study art, magic, and nature.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Arcana, Life, Light, War&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Chaotic Good</content>
    <content contentuid="ha93c965bgccc9g456bg8f0fgac34eae782a4" version="3">Eilistraee is the goddess of good-aligned drow, beauty, song, and freedom. The Dark Maiden desires balance between all races, and struggles against her mother Lolth's corrupt aims.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Life, Light, Nature&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Chaotic Good</content>
    <content contentuid="h37cd82ffga69bg42f5g90e5g104af0637039" version="2">The Watchful Protector is the king of gnomish gods - a deity of humour, gem-cutting, protection, and trickery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Trickery&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Lawful Good</content>
    <content contentuid="h5b75de7cg8d48g4ae7gbc93g380b6e4c7930" version="1">The One-Eye is the orcs' patron deity - a god of war, conquest, and victory at all costs. He has held an ancient and immutable grudge against the elven pantheon since Corellon Larethian took his eye.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Tempest, War&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Chaotic Evil</content>
    <content contentuid="hd5f7fc44gf869g49b9g81eegdbfb8b85ee25" version="1">The Watcher is an eternal sentry among the gods, representing guardians across the planes. After more than a century of fading worship, Helm's power was restored with the Second Sundering.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Life, Light, Twilight&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Lawful Neutral</content>
    <content contentuid="h8b0b8dafg87d7g4e3fg849eg9dda553439e2" version="1">The Crying God protects the oppressed and persecuted. His clergy is sworn to alleviate suffering, even if that means taking on that pain personally.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Life, Twilight&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Lawful Good</content>
    <content contentuid="h3b341b81g6733g4e6dgaf76gaf2fd35fa3df" version="1">Fair but distant, Kelemvor guides the dead to their appropriate plane in the afterlife. His clergy provides last rites across Faerûn, but also destroy undead that have escaped Kelemvor's judgement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Death, Grave&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Lawful Neutral</content>
    <content contentuid="h6d2fcd7fgd2f9g4d6eg9da9g88973de8cd88" version="2">The Exile is the tyrannical patron of the duergar. His clerics are the unquestioned rulers of duergar society, enforcing cold and callous behaviour among his worshippers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Arcana, Death&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Lawful Evil</content>
    <content contentuid="h4e0a9c96gcf4fg4f79ga250g4e593cb51111" version="2">The Morninglord is the god of the dawn and spring, of birth and beginnings. He is invoked to christen both new ventures and new life. His followers embrace growth and renewal, and despise the undead.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Life, Light&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Neutral Good</content>
    <content contentuid="h89834de9g8e77g4a56g8304ge5d37ec38eda" version="3">The much-reviled matriarch of the drow pantheon, Lolth holds sway over spiders, the Underdark, and the wicked creatures of the Demonweb Pits. Her primary goal is to corrupt all drow, transforming them into heartless cultists.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Trickery, War&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Chaotic Evil</content>
    <content contentuid="h92db3ac1g0a2bg4f40gb45egdbe5c255e2cc" version="2">Mielikki is the goddess of forests and the creatures that live within them. She is a remote and spiritual deity, often spoken of in but the quietest of forests.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Nature&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Neutral Good</content>
    <content contentuid="h589eb6adg5d54g4adbgab52gcdad4952765e" version="4">The All-Hammer is a dwarven god worshipped by smiths, artisans, and miners alike. He and Laduguer are constantly at odds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Forge, Knowledge&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Lawful Good</content>
    <content contentuid="h54ca4575g058fg41a2g8960g0e48ebed3072" version="1">As the mother of all magic, Mystra oversees the Weave and spreads arcane knowledge to mortal spellcasters. Her clerics preserve ancient lore and protect bastions of magical energy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Arcana, Knowledge&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Neutral Good</content>
    <content contentuid="hf915b3e4g89c2g4a34gb15dg4724d3465138" version="1">Oghma is the god of inspiration and invention, sharing knowledge with the world through his bards and clerics. Unlike many other deities, Oghma accepts all moral alignments into his clergy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Knowledge&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Neutral</content>
    <content contentuid="h8612a65dg446cg427bga712g7602ce2d2bf3" version="1">The Lady of Silver presides over the moon, stars, and navigation. Her power over the heavens is constantly challenged by her sister Shar, who seeks to plunge the world into eternal shadow.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Knowledge, Life, Twilight&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Chaotic Good</content>
    <content contentuid="h361fbb02g08e7g4d1fg925cgfcfd237ea62e" version="1">As the greater deity of darkness, Shar is feared for her power over the night, secrets, and loss. She is locked in eternal conflict with her twin sister Selûne, goddess of the moon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Death, Trickery&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Neutral Evil</content>
    <content contentuid="he7005f16g879cg492cgad68gf9433c569c0b" version="3">Talos represents the uncaring and destructive force of nature. His followers see life as a set of random effects in a sea of chaos, and take what they can - for who can say when Talos will strike next?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Tempest&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Chaotic Evil</content>
    <content contentuid="ha5d5c929g0827g421fg86c7g1440bdd535fb" version="1">Tempus is the Lord of Battles, overseeing war and its soldiers. He is the embodiment of honourable combat, and condemns needless bloodlust.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: War&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Neutral</content>
    <content contentuid="h43449cdegb4ceg4d65ga235g45e772b9b555" version="1">Tiamat the Many-Mawed is a roiling mass of avarice and hate currently trapped within the Nine Hells. The dragon god of greed eternally plots her escape, as do her many fanatics in world of Toril.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Trickery&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Chaotic Evil</content>
    <content contentuid="ha6c28c36ge9cag4826gbba2g6e854ed05898" version="3">Tymora is the bright-faced goddess of fortune, who favours those who gamble - and set out on adventure - with the utmost skill and daring.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Trickery&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Chaotic Good</content>
    <content contentuid="h25d302cbgb96bg4e7dgb9b7geffcbdff6875" version="1">The Blind God rules over law and justice, encouraging valiant acts from his followers and relentlessly pursuing oathbreakers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Order, War&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Lawful Good</content>
    <content contentuid="h2ed64a9ag586dg451bg9be2g77f8262ed06f" version="2">The Lich Queen is the sole respected leader of the githyanki. She encourages their worship and unquestioning devotion, essentially acting as a deity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: War&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Chaotic Evil</content>
    <content contentuid="h64ee3b0ag999bg4fd3gb0b0ga6ef2481b938" version="3">As the mother of the halfling pantheon, Yondalla is known for her kindness and open mind, encouraging her followers to protect the home, hearth, and nature.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domains: Life, Twilight&lt;br&gt;Alignment: Lawful Good</content>
</contentList>